DAVID INABINETTE

UX Designer & Developer

Web div.designs

Email david.inabinette@gmail.com



I'm a UX designer and developer living in Chicago, IL. I'm passionate about the user's experience and making sure that the product is inclusive and equitable. Whether that's testing across devices or providing accessibility options so the next billion users can enjoy the product.

Skills	Interaction	Visual	Software	Coding
	Wireframing	Sketching	Adobe Suite	HTML
	Mockups	3D Prints	MS Office	CSS/SCSS
	Prototyping	SVG Editing	Figma	Javascript
	User Flows	Drawing	InVision	Git

Experience

Freelancer UX Designer & Developer

Worked with various clients on wireframing, user flows, prototypes, conducted primary research and surveys, and created style guides. Additionally, coded templates and live sites.

April 2018 - Present Remote

Reveal Design Group Project Manager

Coordinated between design teams, contractors, and stakeholders to keep high end architectural projects on schedule.

November 2018 - March 2021 New York City, NY

Education Google Professional Certificate 2021

User Experience (UX) Design

Trident Technical College 2010-2012

General Education & Business

Language English Spanish

Native / Working /

Bilingual Conversational